Viewers, ask the Holy Spirit to reveal Jesus to you.
Ask Him to help cleanse all your wrongs in action, thoughts and deeds - knowingly and unknowingly.
Open your heart, viewers.
Holy Spirit, reveal Jesus to me.
Open my heart, make my heart a contact point.
Do the introduction, Holy Spirit;
do the engagement, Holy Spirit.
Align me, Holy Spirit.
Cleanse all my wrongs in action, thoughts and deeds - knowingly and unknowingly.
Holy Spirit, I need You more.
Introduce me, reveal Jesus to me, make it happen, in Jesus' name.
Viewers, pray the character of the Holy Spirit into your life.
Be the Spirit of adoption to me, Lord.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Make it happen, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Ask God to help you use your talent.
When God helps you to serve Him with all your talent, kings will discover you,
queens will discover you, royalty will discover you, nations will discover you, people will discover you.
Say, "Help me to serve You with all my talents".
Help me to serve You with all my talents.
Viewers, ask God to help you.
Lord Jesus, help me to serve You with all my talent.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Help me to serve You with all my talent, time, money, labour of love. Help me, Lord!
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen.]
Lord, make it happen!
There are many talented people but their talent seems to be dormant -
no one, no king, no queen, no people call for it.
Lord, make it happen!
Reveal their talents to the king and the people, in Jesus' name.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You say you don't have anything - you don't have a job, you don't have this - no!
You are gifted; the gifts are dormant - you need revelation.
Meditation brings revelation.
Begin to meditate on the Word.
Without ceasing, begin to meditate on the Word.
Turn it over and over and over in your heart.
Meditation brings revelation.
Lord, make it happen!
When your talent is honoured and your gift is honoured, joy comes with the peace to serve God.
You are gifted. Where is the gift?
Every God's general in the Bible, their talent was revealed to the king and queen.
Lord, make it happen, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers, begin to remove satan's hand in your life.
You devil, I remove your hand in my life - your hand of failure, sickness, disease be removed!
Your hand of affliction, be removed.
You devil, I remove your hand - your hand of setback and limitation.
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
I command you, remove your hand!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Command the devil to remove his hand from your career, business and family!
Your hand of disunity, affliction, hatred, I remove your hand in the name of Jesus!
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, wherever the affliction is located, I command them out of your life.
No hiding place for affliction.
Never a burden Jesus cannot remove - be removed, in the name of Jesus!
That affliction - out!
Begin to command affliction, sickness, disease wherever it is located,
in your kidneys, liver, blood, command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to command them out!
Dry bones shall rise again!
Are you on the sickbed?
Whatever name you call it, never a sickness Jesus cannot cure; never an affliction Jesus cannot heal.
Command, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers all over the world, bind your spirit to Christ's Spirit.
Begin to bind your spirit to Christ's Spirit - be bound, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, begin to bind your spirit to Christ's Spirit.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray.
Breakthrough!
This is what I am hearing now.
In the name of Jesus, breakthrough!
In the mighty name of Jesus, breakthrough!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name